[
  {
    "front": "grande ville, capitale",
    "back": "都"
  },
  {
    "front": "réunir, même, correspondre, convenir",
    "back": "合"
  },
  {
    "front": "répondre, réponse",
    "back": "答"
  },
  {
    "front": "correct, juste, vrai",
    "back": "正"
  },
  {
    "front": "mauvais, mal",
    "back": "悪"
  },
  {
    "front": "couleur",
    "back": "色"
  },
  {
    "front": "printemps",
    "back": "春"
  },
  {
    "front": "été",
    "back": "夏"
  },
  {
    "front": "automne",
    "back": "秋"
  },
  {
    "front": "hiver",
    "back": "冬"
  }
]
